

#### CONTACT

⊠milliance23@gmail.com

-Rua São Lourenço, 210, casa 21, Nite rói -RI

- 21972141165
- Haitian

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Native Creole
- Intermediary English
- Native French
- Advanced Portuguese

# **SKILLS**

- Python
- Database
- Java
- AngularJS
- React.JS
- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML

# **LINKEDIN**

• https://www.linkedin.com/in/ handyclaude-marie-milliance-95785099

# **GITHUB**

• https://github.com/han19githtbr

#### **PORTFOLIO**

https://portfolio-handy.netlify.app/

# HANDY CLAUDE MARIE MILLIANCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER JR

#### GOAL

I'm looking for a Full Stack development position. I have experience in some languages and technologies in the area, but I am at the beginning of my career and looking for a company where I can grow professionally.

#### SUMMARY

I graduated from the Bachelor's degree in Computer Science at the Federal Rural University of Rio de Janeiro, in June 2022. To gain more experience in the area, I interned in Web Development for 1 year and 4 months at the Attorney General's Office of the Municipality of Nova Iguaçu. I also took a Full Stack development course at TOTI, where I learned how to create complete applications with modern technologies on the market. I am always looking to develop my skills.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Meraki Smart Systems. Remote | 05/2023 - 05/2023

Development and Maintenance of Software and Applications. Technologies and languages used: Angular, C#

# **FULL STACK RESEARCHER AND DEVELOPER**

Connaissance en Action study group. Rio de Janeiro - RJ | 01/2021 - 09/2023

Connaissance en Action is a multidisciplinary study group that aims to develop complete projects and applications using modern market technologies. Technologies and languages used in the project: Angular, Java, Typescript, Spring Boot, MySQL, Git, GitHub.

#### FREELANCE DEVELOPER

**NODRIC STUDIO**. Cabo Frio - RJ | 11/2022 - 12/2022

Development of a website on the WIX platform, for an Architecture company. Technologies and languages used: Html, Css and Javascript.

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

1) Assistance in the development of systems for the needs of the Attorney, as well as support and maintenance of systems. 2) Assistance in the development of the Institutional Website. 3) Provision of support to Public Attorney's employees, aiming to find technological solutions to solve the various problems that arise in daily work. 4) Support for the databases on which the Attorney's systems are based, developed by the IT team. Technologies used: Wordpress, Html, Css, Javascript, Java, Spring Boot.

#### EDUCATION

### **BOOTCAMP SANTANDER FULL STACK JAVA + ANGULAR**

**Santander Universities**. Online | 08/16/2023 - 10/22/2023

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT**

**TOTI**. Rio de Janeiro - RJ | 04/2022 - 08/2022

# **BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE**

Federal Rural University of Rio de Janeiro. Nova Iguaçu - RJ | 04/2014 - 06/2022